

NUR AWAD

• DETAILS •

6186 Tamra, Tamra, 3081100, Israel +972 0548914166 nurawad95@gmail.com

> Date / Place of birth 19/07/1995 California

> > Nationality American

Driving license Yes

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

o SKILLS o

Computer Skills

Fast Learner

Ability to Work in a Team

Editing and Proofreading

Microsoft Office

Editing

Microsoft Excel

• LANGUAGES •

English	
Arabic	
Hebrew	
Spanish	

PROFILE

I am a research assistant for the Learning Disabilities department at the University of Haifa. I am also a freelance editor with several years of experience in editing university-level essays in English. As an English native speaker and MA graduate of English Literature, I possess the necessary background and skills for the process of editing.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Freelance Editor and Proofreader

February 2020 — Present

Research Assistant at the Learning Disabilities Department at the University of Haifa,

May 2017 — Present

My work includes producing content for experiments primarily in English. My responsibilities include creating content for experiments, organizing the data post-experiment, and coding the data through Excel.

English Teacher/Coordinator at Everest Center for Bagrut and Tutoring, Tamra

November 2016 — June 2019

My responsibilities included private tutoring and creating multiple curriculums for different ages and groups. In addition to teaching grammar and writing to middle school students, I also prepared high school students for their English bagrut exams.

Conversational English Teacher at Kabul High School, Kabul

February 2018 — May 2018

This was a temporary position for a high school conversation program. I taught four classes of 10th graders how and when to say various phrases in certain contexts in English.

EDUCATION

MA in English Literature, University of Haifa, Haifa

October 2018 — October 2020

Graduated with honors with an average of 89.

BA in English Literature, University of Haifa, Haifa

October 2014 — February 2018

Graduated with an average of 87.

COURSES

Proofread like a Pro, Udemy

February 2021 — February 2021

Complete Punctuation: Novice to Pro, Udemy

February 2021 — February 2021

¶ REFERENCES

References available upon request